{
    "id": "0227ba0c194643af962bfe84c5276ef9",
    "title": "Conditional sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "bbcf74c5e8fa4bb1abdea4a82f6c5392",
            "title": "Conditional Sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If I were you, I ………………… tolerate this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will not",
                        "would not",
                        "would not have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If she asked more politely, he …………………. her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will help",
                        "would help",
                        "would have helped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If she ………………… there, she wouldn’t have been killed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't go",
                        "hasn't gone",
                        "hadn't gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I …………………. about his predicament, I would have helped him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "knew",
                        "had known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Should he be late, we …………………. to start without him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will have",
                        "would have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. in bad trouble, if she hadn’t helped me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be",
                        "would be",
                        "would have been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I had another $500, I ………………… a car.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can buy",
                        "could buy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you did that, you ………………….. probably be in trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you like it, ………………….. you buy it?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you should happen to finish early, …………………. you give me a ring?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}